[
   {
      "prompt":"You can either study for the upcoming test, or rest for the upcoming race.",
      "options":[
         {
            "response":"I will study for the test.",
            "stats":{
               "charisma":-10,
               "athletic ability":-10,
               "smartness":10
            }
         },
         {
            "response":"I will rest for the race.",
            "stats":{
               "charisma":10,
               "athletic ability":5,
               "smartness":-5
            }
         }
      ]
   },
   {
      "prompt":"You are invited to play dnd with the nerds but also invited to play football with the jocks, which one do you chose?",
      "options":[
         {
            "response":"Nerds",
            "stats":{
               "charisma":-10,
               "athletic ability":-10,
               "smartness":10
            }
         },
         {
            "response":"Jocks",
            "stats":{
               "charisma":10,
               "athletic ability":10,
               "smartness":-10
            }
         }
      ]
   },
   {
      "prompt":"The popular kids invite you to a party but you have a test tomorrow",
      "options":[
         {
            "response":"Go to the party",
            "stats":{
               "charisma":10,
               "athletic ability":4,
               "smartness":-10
            }
         },
         {
            "response":"Study",
            "stats":{
               "charisma":-7,
               "athletic ability":-4,
               "smartness":10
            }
         }
      ]
   },
   {
      "prompt":"A girl asks you out and you declined it now the girl is sad, what do you do?",
      "options":[
         {
            "response":"Make her feel better",
            "stats":{
               "charisma":10,
               "athletic ability":-4,
               "smartness":-8
            }
         },
         {
            "response":"Ignore it",
            "stats":{
               "charisma":-10,
               "athletic ability":0,
               "smartness":0
            }
         }
      ]
   },
   {
      "prompt":"Some jocks invited you to have lunch with them",
      "options":[
         {
            "response":"I will eat with them",
            "stats":{
               "charisma":5,
               "athletic ablity":10,
               "smartness":-10
            }
         },
         {
            "response":"I won't eat with them",
            "stats":{
               "charisma":-5,
               "athletic ablity":-5,
               "smartness":10
            }
         }
      ]
   },
   {
      "prompt":"A friend invites you over for a sleepover the night before a test",
      "options":[
         {
            "response":"Sleepover!",
            "stats":{
               "charisma":10,
               "athletic ablity":0,
               "smartness":0
            }
         },
         {
            "response":"Reject their offer",
            "stats":{
               "charisma":-10,
               "athletic ablity":0,
               "smartness":5
            }
         }
      ]
   },
   {
      "prompt":"You get asked out ~nice~!",
      "options":[
         {
            "response":"Reject them",
            "stats":{
               "charisma":-10,
               "athletic ablity":0,
               "smartness":-5
            }
         },
         {
            "response":"Go on a date!",
            "stats":{
               "charisma":10,
               "athletic ablity":0,
               "smartness":0
            }
         }
      ]
   },
   {
      "prompt":"Some geeks ask you game with them while some jocks ask you to hangout",
      "options":[
         {
            "response":"Game with the geeks",
            "stats":{
               "charisma":-10,
               "athletic ablity":-5,
               "smartness":10
            }
         },
         {
            "response":"Hang with the jocks",
            "stats":{
               "charisma":10,
               "athletic ablity":5,
               "smartness":-10
            }
         }
      ]
   },
   {
      "prompt":"You accidentally bump into one of the popular girls",
      "options":[
         {
            "response":"Apologize",
            "stats":{
               "charisma":0,
               "athletic ablity":0,
               "smartness":1
            }
         },
         {
            "response":"Ask her out",
            "stats":{
               "charisma":-10,
               "athletic ablity":0,
               "smartness":-10
            }
         },
         {
            "response":"Run away",
            "stats":{
               "charisma":-5,
               "athletic ablity":5,
               "smartness":-5
            }
         }
      ]
   },
   {
      "prompt":"During astrology class someone says aliens don't exist",
      "options":[
         {
            "response":"Prove them wrong.",
            "stats":{
               "charisma":-100,
               "athletic ablity":-100,
               "smartness":-100
            }
         },
         {
            "response":"Argue with them",
            "stats":{
               "charisma":-5,
               "athletic ablity":0,
               "smartness":5
            }
         },
         {
            "response":"Say nothing",
            "stats":{
               "charisma":0,
               "athletic ablity":0,
               "smartness":0
            }
         }
      ]
   },
   {
      "prompt":"You walk up to a vending machine to get a drink",
      "options":[
         {
            "response":"Drink a soda",
            "stats":{
               "charisma":0,
               "athletic ablity":-5,
               "smartness":0
            }
         },
         {
            "response":"Drink some water",
            "stats":{
               "charisma":0,
               "athletic ablity":5,
               "smartness":0
            }
         }
      ]
   },
   {
      "prompt":"You sit down next to one of the popular kids on the bus",
      "options":[
         {
            "response":"Say nothing",
            "stats":{
               "charisma":-5,
               "athletic ablity":0,
               "smartness":0
            }
         },
         {
            "response":"Tell a joke",
            "stats":{
               "charisma":10,
               "athletic ablity":0,
               "smartness":0
            }
         }
      ]
   }
]
